<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>News Archives - Preference Center | Mattel</title>
	<atom:link href="https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/category/news/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/category/news/</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 14:25:32 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.2.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Yellowstone tourists put newborn elk calf in car, drive to police station</title>
		<link>https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/yellowstone-tourists-put-newborn-elk-calf-in-car-drive-to-police-station/</link>
					<comments>https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/yellowstone-tourists-put-newborn-elk-calf-in-car-drive-to-police-station/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 14:25:32 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/?p=40</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>When officials at national parks warn visitors not to interfere or mess with animals, some take that advice and some don&#8217;t. Over Memorial Day weekend, tourists decided to take matters into their own hands when coming upon a newborn elk. “During the Memorial Day weekend, visitors placed an elk calf in their car while likely ... <a title="Yellowstone tourists put newborn elk calf in car, drive to police station" class="read-more" href="https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/yellowstone-tourists-put-newborn-elk-calf-in-car-drive-to-police-station/" aria-label="More on Yellowstone tourists put newborn elk calf in car, drive to police station">Read more</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/yellowstone-tourists-put-newborn-elk-calf-in-car-drive-to-police-station/">Yellowstone tourists put newborn elk calf in car, drive to police station</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://test-preference-center.mattel.com">Preference Center  | Mattel</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>When officials at national parks warn visitors not to interfere or mess with animals, some take that advice and some don&#8217;t.</p>
<p>Over Memorial Day weekend, tourists decided to take matters into their own hands when coming upon a newborn elk.</p>
<p>“During the Memorial Day weekend, visitors placed an elk calf in their car while likely driving on U.S. Highway 191 in the park and brought the newborn to the West Yellowstone, Montana, Police Department,” officials said in a report, according to outsider.com.</p>
<p>“The elk [calf] later ran off into the forest and its condition is unknown,&#8221; the report states.</p>
<p>Even if the tourists were trying to do a good deed, violators can face some serious penalties.</p>
<p>SPORTS NEWSLETTERSign up now for daily updates sent to your inbox</p>
<p>Yellowstone National Park mandates visitors must “stay at least 100 yards (91 m) away from bears and wolves, and at least 25 yards (23 m) away from all other animals, including bison and elk.&#8221;</p>
<p>Those who break the law face fines and jail time. Last month, a man pleaded guilty to one count of feeding, touching, teasing, frightening, or intentionally disturbing wildlife. He received a $500 fine and was required to make other payments to Yellowstone.</p>
<p>If that doesn&#8217;t make people listen to park officials, maybe this warning from them will.</p>
<p>&#8220;Yellowstone’s scenic wonders are sure to take your breath away: don’t let them take your life,&#8221; officials say on the website.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/yellowstone-tourists-put-newborn-elk-calf-in-car-drive-to-police-station/">Yellowstone tourists put newborn elk calf in car, drive to police station</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://test-preference-center.mattel.com">Preference Center  | Mattel</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/yellowstone-tourists-put-newborn-elk-calf-in-car-drive-to-police-station/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How one quiet Illinois college town became the symbol of abortion rights in America</title>
		<link>https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/how-one-quiet-illinois-college-town-became-the-symbol-of-abortion-rights-in-america/</link>
					<comments>https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/how-one-quiet-illinois-college-town-became-the-symbol-of-abortion-rights-in-america/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 14:24:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/?p=37</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>CARBONDALE, Ill. – The 26-year-old had never heard of the distant southern Illinois town, but it had become the closest option. So she cobbled together money. Found child care. Asked her brother for a ride. And set off early one morning to drive north across state lines to 22,000-person Carbondale. It was a nearly seven-hour ... <a title="How one quiet Illinois college town became the symbol of abortion rights in America" class="read-more" href="https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/how-one-quiet-illinois-college-town-became-the-symbol-of-abortion-rights-in-america/" aria-label="More on How one quiet Illinois college town became the symbol of abortion rights in America">Read more</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/how-one-quiet-illinois-college-town-became-the-symbol-of-abortion-rights-in-america/">How one quiet Illinois college town became the symbol of abortion rights in America</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://test-preference-center.mattel.com">Preference Center  | Mattel</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>CARBONDALE, Ill. – The 26-year-old had never heard of the distant southern Illinois town, but it had become the closest option.</p>
<p>So she cobbled together money. Found child care. Asked her brother for a ride. And set off early one morning to drive north across state lines to 22,000-person Carbondale.</p>
<p>It was a nearly seven-hour round trip from her home in Tennessee. Long enough for the decision to rattle in her head as the flat Midwestern landscape slipped by the car windows.</p>
<p>No, she told herself. I thought it out. It&#8217;s not the right moment to have a child.</p>
<p>She was already raising two young children. She had split with her boyfriend. She was financially unstable from losing a job. And she could face health risks.</p>
<p>She finally tried to go to sleep.</p>
<p>They crossed into Illinois.</p>
<p>From there it was another hour’s drive to the outskirts of Carbondale, a place often reached by a two-lane state highway that winds by farm fields and churches or a busier route dotted with fast food, strip malls and a building on which, for a time, hung a banner reading, “Pro Life. Pro God. Pro Gun. Pro Trump.”</p>
<p>Mostly rural, conservative southern Illinois was an unexpected place for an abortion clinic, the 26-year-old thought, even if the town’s welcome sign noted it was home to Southern Illinois University.</p>
<p>They parked outside a single-story office building, across from a Kroger, at the Choices Center for Reproductive Health. She walked in past a security guard to a waiting room, donning a green wristband.</p>
<p>When it became clear Roe v. Wade would be overturned, Choices Center for Reproductive Health looked to move abortion services from Memphis to Carbondale, Illinois, where abortion would remain legal. Choices braced for expected anti-abortion demonstrations and hired a security guard.<br />
TOP AND ABOVE LEFT: NICOLE HESTER, THE TENNESSEAN/USA TODAY NETWORK; ABOVE RIGHT: CHRIS KENNING, USA TODAY<br />
Soon she sat on an exam table.</p>
<p>Outside, a staffer put a mark on a whiteboard grid where the center kept track of its days, a row for each of six rooms, a column for each of the four people a patient would wait to see, including a nurse and a medical provider. Once each row was checked off, one patient was done; the next one could begin. Nearby, receptionists scheduled appointments for patients from as far away as Texas and Mississippi.</p>
<p>After medical checks and an explanation of what to expect, the woman with the green wristband lifted a small water bottle and swallowed the first of two pills that would end her pregnancy.</p>
<p>Similar scenes play out each day five miles away, a short drive past the city’s Amtrak station, downtown shops and neon-lit 1950s-era Dairy Queen, on the other side of town. There, at an anodyne medical office where a vinyl sign stuck in the grass reads “Alamo Women’s Clinic,” the parking lot is often filled with out-of-state license plates – women who drive as long as 10 hours from the Deep South for an abortion.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/how-one-quiet-illinois-college-town-became-the-symbol-of-abortion-rights-in-america/">How one quiet Illinois college town became the symbol of abortion rights in America</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://test-preference-center.mattel.com">Preference Center  | Mattel</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/how-one-quiet-illinois-college-town-became-the-symbol-of-abortion-rights-in-america/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>HSN just launched an adorable new collection ahead of &#8216;The Little Mermaid&#8217; premiere</title>
		<link>https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/hsn-just-launched-an-adorable-new-collection-ahead-of-the-little-mermaid-premiere/</link>
					<comments>https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/hsn-just-launched-an-adorable-new-collection-ahead-of-the-little-mermaid-premiere/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 14:23:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/?p=34</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>If you know a little one who&#8217;s been eagerly awaiting the release of Disney&#8217;s &#8220;The Little Mermaid,&#8221; they&#8217;re in luck—this week, HSN dropped a new collection of toys, home goods and more inspired by the magical new film. While you have to wait until Friday, May 26, to catch the movie in theaters, the HSN ... <a title="HSN just launched an adorable new collection ahead of &#8216;The Little Mermaid&#8217; premiere" class="read-more" href="https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/hsn-just-launched-an-adorable-new-collection-ahead-of-the-little-mermaid-premiere/" aria-label="More on HSN just launched an adorable new collection ahead of &#8216;The Little Mermaid&#8217; premiere">Read more</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/hsn-just-launched-an-adorable-new-collection-ahead-of-the-little-mermaid-premiere/">HSN just launched an adorable new collection ahead of &#8216;The Little Mermaid&#8217; premiere</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://test-preference-center.mattel.com">Preference Center  | Mattel</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>If you know a little one who&#8217;s been eagerly awaiting the release of Disney&#8217;s &#8220;The Little Mermaid,&#8221; they&#8217;re in luck—this week, HSN dropped a new collection of toys, home goods and more inspired by the magical new film. While you have to wait until Friday, May 26, to catch the movie in theaters, the HSN x Little Mermaid collection is available to shop today.</p>
<p>Know an aspiring singer? They&#8217;d love the Live Action Little Mermaid Boombox, which is on sale for just $29 (Save $10). The clamshell-shaped boombox comes with a small microphone so your little one can belt along with Ariel and the soundtrack.</p>
<p>If they&#8217;d rather add to their doll collection, you can pick up the Little Mermaid Singing Doll for just $24.99. This Ariel doll features a shell button that plays &#8220;Part of Your World&#8221; when pressed. If you&#8217;d like the doll without the singing, you can pick it up for just $14.99.</p>
<p>Here are all the best &#8220;The Little Mermaid&#8221; toys and more you can shop at HSN right now.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/hsn-just-launched-an-adorable-new-collection-ahead-of-the-little-mermaid-premiere/">HSN just launched an adorable new collection ahead of &#8216;The Little Mermaid&#8217; premiere</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://test-preference-center.mattel.com">Preference Center  | Mattel</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/hsn-just-launched-an-adorable-new-collection-ahead-of-the-little-mermaid-premiere/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Mattel Announces New Product Collection to Celebrate the Upcoming Movie, Barbie™</title>
		<link>https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/mattel-announces-new-product-collection-to-celebrate-the-upcoming-movie-barbie/</link>
					<comments>https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/mattel-announces-new-product-collection-to-celebrate-the-upcoming-movie-barbie/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 11:37:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/?p=16</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>EL SEGUNDO, Calif.&#8211;(BUSINESS WIRE)&#8211;Mattel, Inc. (NASDAQ: MAT) announced today a new collection from across the portfolio of Mattel brands inspired by the highly anticipated film, Barbie™. Created in partnership with Warner Bros. Pictures, the upcoming movie, Barbie™, debuts in theaters nationwide July 21st. Fans can now take home a part of the movie and play ... <a title="Mattel Announces New Product Collection to Celebrate the Upcoming Movie, Barbie™" class="read-more" href="https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/mattel-announces-new-product-collection-to-celebrate-the-upcoming-movie-barbie/" aria-label="More on Mattel Announces New Product Collection to Celebrate the Upcoming Movie, Barbie™">Read more</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/mattel-announces-new-product-collection-to-celebrate-the-upcoming-movie-barbie/">Mattel Announces New Product Collection to Celebrate the Upcoming Movie, Barbie™</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://test-preference-center.mattel.com">Preference Center  | Mattel</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>EL SEGUNDO, Calif.&#8211;(BUSINESS WIRE)&#8211;Mattel, Inc. (NASDAQ: MAT) announced today a new collection from across the portfolio of Mattel brands inspired by the highly anticipated film, Barbie<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />. Created in partnership with Warner Bros. Pictures, the upcoming movie, Barbie<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />, debuts in theaters nationwide July 21st. Fans can now take home a part of the movie and play out even more stories with toys from brands including UNO®, Hot Wheels®, Fisher-Price®, MEGA<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> and Barbie.</p>
<p>The line of Barbie<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> the Movie dolls features looks fans will see in the movie, reflecting the signature styles of Barbie, Ken, and new characters as they traverse through Barbie Land and beyond. The collection emulates the Barbiecore<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> and Ken-ergy<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> felt in the feature film, from their first-look outfits to the matching sets worn in the movie. Best of all – the collection features several recognizable and must-have accessories, including a mini replica of the iconic three-story DreamHouse<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> from MEGA and a stunning pink RC Corvette® from Hot Wheels.</p>
<p>“Barbie the movie is a monumental moment for the brand, and we cannot wait for fans to experience Barbie like never before on the big screen,” said Lisa McKnight, Executive Vice President and Global Head of Barbie &amp; Dolls, Mattel. “The new line of Barbie the movie Mattel toys perfectly captures the fun and joy of Barbie that is at the heart of the film. This collection allows fans of all ages to celebrate their favorite characters and scenes from the movie. What an incredible way to kick off the summer of Barbie!”</p>
<p>Barbie<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> The Movie doll line includes:</p>
<ul>
<li>Barbie The Movie Doll Pink Gingham Dress: Models a vintage-inspired pink and white gingham dress, complete with daisy chain necklace and pastel pink heart-adorned pumps.</li>
<li>
Barbie The Movie Ken Doll Pastel Stripe Matching Set: Wears a beachy, pink and mint green striped matching set with surfboard in tow.</li>
<li>
Barbie The Movie Doll Plaid Matching Set: Touts an impeccably coordinated three-piece matching pastel plaid set with puffy skirt, cropped jacket, and matching blouse.</li>
<li>
Barbie The Movie Ken Doll Denim Matching Set: Clad in an all-Demin look with an open vest and matching light wash jeans, featuring a glimpse of iconic Ken boxers.</li>
<li>
Barbie The Movie Doll Gold Disco Jumpsuit: Shines in a sequined disco jumpsuit featuring big disco hair, metallic jewelry and golden heels.</li>
<li>
Barbie The Movie Doll Pink Western Outfit: Wears an eye-catching, Western-themed matching pink denim vest and flare jeans with a cowboy hat and boots.</li>
<li>
Barbie The Movie Doll Gloria Pink Power Pantsuit: Looks fierce in a three-piece pink suit featuring satiny blazer, matching blouse, and pinstriped trousers with fashionably split cuffs.</li>
<li>
Barbie The Movie Ken Doll Gold and White Disco Tracksuit: Embodies luxe quality and casual style in a white tracksuit with metallic gold color-blocked sleeves and a shiny “K” accent to add star power to the ensemble.</li>
<li>
Barbie The Movie Doll President in Pink and Gold Dress: Wears a full, satiny gown that features a sparkly off-shoulder bodice and shimmery gold accents that trail down her skirt.</li>
<li>
Barbie The Movie Fashion Pack: Includes three iconic Barbie outfits from the movie: a blue and white sundress, gingham pink blouse and short set, and dreamy pajama outfit.</li>
<li>
Barbie The Movie Pink Corvette Convertible: Featuring a curvy retro silhouette and pink paint job, with film-inspired details like white wall tires and chrome rims.</li>
<li>
Along with Barbie items inspired by the characters in the movie, Barbie<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />, Mattel is also releasing a collection of products celebrating the live action feature film across the larger Mattel portfolio, including:</li>
</ul>
<p>UNO Barbie The Movie: Deck features graphics inspired by characters and scenes from Barbie The Movie – including a special “Played With Too Much” rule that will have players both discarding and drawing cards.<br />
Little People Collector Barbie The Movie: Bringing four of the film’s iconic characters down to Little People figure size and styled in memorable outfits including Barbie, President Barbie, Ken, and Gloria.<br />
Barbie The Movie MEGA Dreamhouse: Buildable replica of Barbie’s iconic 3-story DreamHouse as seen in the film, including spiral staircase, pool, and slide.<br />
Barbie The Movie Hot Wheels RC Barbie Corvette: Radio-controlled 1956 Corvette Stingray that can fit two Barbie dolls to create authentic road trips with Barbie.<br />
Barbie The Movie Hot Wheels Die-Cast Pink Corvette in 1:64 Scale: Features Barbie deco – in Barbie pink – as a Hot Wheels 1:64 scale die-cast car.<br />
The Mattel collection of the movie Barbie<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/14.0.0/72x72/2122.png" alt="™" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> products, available in collectible packaging, will be at retailers nationwide and/or Mattel Shop for an SRP of $1.25 to $150 starting June 1st.</p>
<p>In continued celebration of the film, Mattel will also be releasing an array of movie-themed products with over 100 brand partners across fashion, beauty, accessories and more starting this month.</p>
<p>About Barbie The Movie</p>
<p>To live in Barbie Land is to be a perfect being in a perfect place. Unless you have a full-on existential crisis. Or you’re a Ken. Warner Bros. Pictures Presents A Heyday Films Production, A LuckyChap Entertainment Production, An NB/GG Pictures Production, A Mattel Production, “BARBIE,” directed by Greta Gerwig, starring Margot Robbie, Ryan Gosling, America Ferrera, Kate McKinnon, Issa Rae, Rhea Perlman, and Will Ferrell. The film is written by Greta Gerwig &amp; Noah Baumbach, based on “Barbie” by Mattel, and produced by David Heyman, Margot Robbie, Tom Ackerley and Robbie Brenner. The executive producers are Gerwig, Baumbach, Ynon Kreiz, Richard Dickson, Michael Sharp, Josey McNamara, Courtenay Valenti, Toby Emmerich and Cate Adams. The film will be distributed worldwide by Warner Bros. Pictures and released in theaters only nationwide on July 21, 2023 and internationally beginning 19 July 2023.</p>
<p>About Mattel</p>
<p>Mattel is a leading global toy company and owner of one of the strongest catalogs of children’s and family entertainment franchises in the world. We create innovative products and experiences that inspire, entertain, and develop children through play. We engage consumers through our portfolio of iconic brands, including Barbie®, Hot Wheels®, Fisher-Price®, American Girl®, Thomas &amp; Friends®, UNO®, Masters of the Universe®, Monster High® and MEGA®, as well as other popular intellectual properties that we own or license in partnership with global entertainment companies. Our offerings include film and television content, gaming and digital experiences, music, and live events. We operate in 35 locations and our products are available in more than 150 countries in collaboration with the world’s leading retail and ecommerce companies. Since its founding in 1945, Mattel is proud to be a trusted partner in empowering children to explore the wonder of childhood and reach their full potential. Visit us online at mattel.com.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/mattel-announces-new-product-collection-to-celebrate-the-upcoming-movie-barbie/">Mattel Announces New Product Collection to Celebrate the Upcoming Movie, Barbie™</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://test-preference-center.mattel.com">Preference Center  | Mattel</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/mattel-announces-new-product-collection-to-celebrate-the-upcoming-movie-barbie/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Elden Ring and Hogwarts Legacy Could Be in the Same Boat in One Magical Way</title>
		<link>https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/elden-ring-and-hogwarts-legacy-could-be-in-the-same-boat-in-one-magical-way/</link>
					<comments>https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/elden-ring-and-hogwarts-legacy-could-be-in-the-same-boat-in-one-magical-way/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 11:34:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Game]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/?p=13</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Elden Ring and Hogwarts Legacy are two fairly different games. While Elden Ring is a melee-focused, brutally difficult journey through a wonderfully dark and oppressive fantasy world, Hogwarts Legacy is a bit more of a whimsical, lighthearted, and magical adventure through one of the most nostalgic locations in all of popular culture, with spell-based combat ... <a title="Elden Ring and Hogwarts Legacy Could Be in the Same Boat in One Magical Way" class="read-more" href="https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/elden-ring-and-hogwarts-legacy-could-be-in-the-same-boat-in-one-magical-way/" aria-label="More on Elden Ring and Hogwarts Legacy Could Be in the Same Boat in One Magical Way">Read more</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/elden-ring-and-hogwarts-legacy-could-be-in-the-same-boat-in-one-magical-way/">Elden Ring and Hogwarts Legacy Could Be in the Same Boat in One Magical Way</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://test-preference-center.mattel.com">Preference Center  | Mattel</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Elden Ring and Hogwarts Legacy are two fairly different games. While Elden Ring is a melee-focused, brutally difficult journey through a wonderfully dark and oppressive fantasy world, Hogwarts Legacy is a bit more of a whimsical, lighthearted, and magical adventure through one of the most nostalgic locations in all of popular culture, with spell-based combat and calm exploration being the focus of its own gameplay.</p>
<p>That being said, Elden Ring and Hogwarts Legacy aren&#8217;t totally opposed to one another. Both games use a third-person perspective, both put an emphasis on open-world exploration, and most interestingly, both have their fair share of magic spells. But when it comes to Elden Ring and Hogwarts Legacy&#8217;s magic, both games could find themselves in the same boat pretty soon.</p>
<p>In the past, FromSoftware games have had some notoriously lackluster magic combat options. While there were always plenty of spells in the Dark Souls trilogy, the vast majority of the offensive spell types felt simply too weak in practice, leaving them pretty redundant when compared to the game&#8217;s melee options. With Elden Ring, FromSoftware sought to finally change this, and for the most part, it succeeded.</p>
<p>At launch, Elden Ring boasted an eye-watering total of 171 magical spells, covering both Incantations and Sorceries. For reference, Skyrim has 96 spells. What&#8217;s even more impressive than the sheer quantity of Elden Ring&#8217;s spells is the quality of them. While not all of them are wholly original, and many are upgraded versions of base spells that essentially just add another projectile to the cast, almost every spell in Elden Ring is worth picking for one reason or another, and each one has its own visually-impressive, unique animation and effect.</p>
<p>But Elden Ring is set to receive a large-scale expansion soon, and it could run into a big issue with its magic. Titled Elden Ring Shadow of the Erdtree, this DLC expansion is set to be the biggest DLC that FromSoftware has ever produced, which is really saying something. So, naturally, fans can probably expect to see a slew of new spells in the game. But with 171 spells already available, Elden Ring&#8217;s DLC might not be able to really add anything that fans haven&#8217;t already seen.</p>
<p>Hogwarts Legacy could end up being in a similar boat. Though Hogwarts Legacy has much fewer spells than Elden Ring, clocking in at only 31, a lot of effort has seemingly gone into making each one feel truly distinct and worthwhile, with unique visuals, animations, and effects across the board for each one. Hogwarts Legacy&#8217;s current spells really cover just about everything that players could need or want from a Harry Potter game, with offensive spells like Stupefy and Flipendo, utility charms like Lumos and Reparo, and even all three Unforgivable Curses.</p>
<p>If Hogwarts Legacy ever receives its long-rumored DLC, it&#8217;ll surely add a good few new spells to the game, just like Elden Ring&#8217;s Shadow of the Erdtree, but really there isn&#8217;t a big need for them. Though many fans are desperate to see iconic spells like Expecto Patronum, Reducto, and Confundo come to Hogwarts Legacy, they might end up feeling a little redundant, with Hogwarts Legacy&#8217;s current spell list covering pretty much all the bases from a purely technical and gameplay standpoint. So, much like Elden Ring, Hogwarts Legacy would have a tough time making any additional DLC spells stand out from the crowd.</p>
<p>&nbsp;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/elden-ring-and-hogwarts-legacy-could-be-in-the-same-boat-in-one-magical-way/">Elden Ring and Hogwarts Legacy Could Be in the Same Boat in One Magical Way</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://test-preference-center.mattel.com">Preference Center  | Mattel</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/elden-ring-and-hogwarts-legacy-could-be-in-the-same-boat-in-one-magical-way/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>How Zelda: Tears of the Kingdom Breaks the Cycle Started by Zelda: Skyward Sword</title>
		<link>https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/how-zelda-tears-of-the-kingdom-breaks-the-cycle-started-by-zelda-skyward-sword/</link>
					<comments>https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/how-zelda-tears-of-the-kingdom-breaks-the-cycle-started-by-zelda-skyward-sword/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 11:32:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Game]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/?p=10</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Within the grand scheme of Zelda&#8217;s many timelines, it seems that The Legend of Zelda: Tears of the Kingdom might be the closing chapter to The Legend of Zelda: Skyward Sword and serves as a bookend to the game where the cycle first began. Before its release, many had speculated about the possible connections The ... <a title="How Zelda: Tears of the Kingdom Breaks the Cycle Started by Zelda: Skyward Sword" class="read-more" href="https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/how-zelda-tears-of-the-kingdom-breaks-the-cycle-started-by-zelda-skyward-sword/" aria-label="More on How Zelda: Tears of the Kingdom Breaks the Cycle Started by Zelda: Skyward Sword">Read more</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/how-zelda-tears-of-the-kingdom-breaks-the-cycle-started-by-zelda-skyward-sword/">How Zelda: Tears of the Kingdom Breaks the Cycle Started by Zelda: Skyward Sword</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://test-preference-center.mattel.com">Preference Center  | Mattel</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>Within the grand scheme of Zelda&#8217;s many timelines, it seems that The Legend of Zelda: Tears of the Kingdom might be the closing chapter to The Legend of Zelda: Skyward Sword and serves as a bookend to the game where the cycle first began. Before its release, many had speculated about the possible connections The Legend of Zelda: Tears of the Kingdom might have with other games from across the series, with most theories focusing on Skyward Sword and Twilight Princess. But Tears of the Kingdom&#8217;s story and its position within Zelda&#8217;s timelines could suggest that the cycle may finally be broken.</p>
<p>By examining various details from across Tears of the Kingdom, such as its story, its themes, and its imagery, it&#8217;s possible to piece together how exactly Nintendo&#8217;s latest Zelda game connects all the way back to Skyward Sword. Though not the first ever published Zelda game, it caused controversy for canonizing the most essential Zelda lore despite eventually being considered the series&#8217; worst game to date. But Tears of the Kingdom might have redeemed Skyward Sword by creating a narrative and gameplay experience that endeavors to resolve its predecessor&#8217;s mistakes, ultimately providing closure to both it and Breath of the Wild.</p>
<p>From the start of Tears of the Kingdom&#8217;s story, the game introduces and explains the mythos of the Zonai. Though they were included in passing references in Breath of the Wild, Tears of the Kingdom expands on this new lore by suggesting that long before Hyrule had even formed that the Zonai had come down from the heavens. While they didn&#8217;t believe they were gods, Rauru acknowledges that the technology of Constructs, Zonai devices, and Secret Stones would have given that impression. Despite this, Rauru still established himself as king and took a Hylian wife, and this is claimed to be the origin of Hyrule&#8217;s founding.</p>
<p>However, this conflicts with the canon that Skyward Sword establishes, as its story suggests that Zelda and Link remain on the surface and form the first kingdom of Hyrule. But while there are some details that might contradict one another, it is possible to join the two narratives together. For instance, both games make reference to how sky islands serve to protect others from evil, how advanced beings came down from the sky, and how the lines blur between the supernatural and technological. With a small adjustment, it&#8217;s arguable that Tears of the Kingdom is continuing from Skyward Sword&#8217;s canon.</p>
<p>What serves as a linchpin to this theory though is Fi. Though she has been regarded by fans as the worst companion in Zelda, Fi has seen recent defense as a great concept just badly executed. Despite claiming to be a spirit created by the Goddess Hylia, Fi is without question presented as if she were an artificial intelligence, which could mean she actually has Zonai origins with her history being rewritten. This theory is strengthened in Tears of the Kingdom by its story focusing on restoring the Master Sword, Fi&#8217;s theme from Skyward Sword playing during cutscenes, and the sword &#8220;responding&#8221; to other characters.</p>
<p>In its prologue, Skyward Sword explains how the likes of Skyloft and other islands came into existence, stating that fissures opened up on the surface and let loose evil forces. This is uncannily similar to Tears of the Kingdom and the event that it dubs the &#8220;Upheaval,&#8221; which chasms opening up across Hyrule that Gloom emanates from. Throughout Zelda, many games have references to an &#8220;Underworld&#8221; which was claimed to be where Ganondorf and his minions resided. This too is also reflected in Tears of the Kingdom, with Ganondorf&#8217;s armies populating the Depths and where Ganondorf himself has made his lair beneath Hyrule Castle.</p>
<p>Similarly, as the forebear to Ganondorf, Demise is also described to be the Demon King who commands an army from beneath the earth. But more specifically, during Skyward Sword&#8217;s story, it is revealed that Demise is attempting to break free from a seal he was placed under long ago, with the player encountering a boss named &#8220;The Imprisoned&#8221; on multiple occasions. Tears of the Kingdom again appears to directly parallel this narrative, with Ganondorf attempting to break free of a seal placed on him during &#8220;The Imprisoning War.&#8221; While Ganondorf is the reincarnation of Demise, the connections seem too close to just be self-referential.</p>
<p>Much like Fi, there is evidence that supports the theory that Tears of the Kingdom&#8217;s and Skyward Sword&#8217;s parallels are more than they seem, and it can be seen with Ganondorf after he has one of the Secret Stones. Not only do these Secret Stones bear a resemblance to Skyward Sword&#8217;s Sacred Tears which further ties into Tears of the Kingdom&#8217;s subtitle, but Ganondorf&#8217;s transformation further evokes the same look of Demise once he has been resurrected. Between flowing fiery tendrils of hair and his body pulsing with Malice or Gloom, Tears of the Kingdom presents its version of Ganondorf as Demise in everything but name.</p>
<p>Between Skyward Sword, Tears of the Kingdom, and Beyond</p>
<p>Though the Zelda series isn&#8217;t likely to end with Tears of the Kingdom as its ultimate finale, especially since a new Zelda game is supposedly already being planned, it&#8217;s possible that just as Skyward Sword began the timeline, Tears of the Kingdom appears to end it. Breath of the Wild had already been confirmed by Nintendo as the supposed inevitable endpoint of Zelda&#8217;s three branching timelines, and as its sequel so too does Tears of the Kingdom. It would therefore make sense in Zelda&#8217;s larger narrative to have the closure of these branching timelines directly engage with the legacy Skyward Sword had first set out.</p>
<p>With this in mind, the series could still live on with Zelda games set between the two endpoints of Skyward Sword and Tears of the Kingdom as the latter emphasizes the millennia of history Hyrule has. But this could be Nintendo&#8217;s plan to redress the errors from Skyward Sword, from small details like perfecting the use of stamina to the large such as perfecting a world within the sky, and ultimately perform a soft reboot. Until now, speculation around Zelda&#8217;s timelines has overshadowed each game&#8217;s release, so Tears of the Kingdom could start a new Zelda timeline altogether.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/how-zelda-tears-of-the-kingdom-breaks-the-cycle-started-by-zelda-skyward-sword/">How Zelda: Tears of the Kingdom Breaks the Cycle Started by Zelda: Skyward Sword</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://test-preference-center.mattel.com">Preference Center  | Mattel</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/how-zelda-tears-of-the-kingdom-breaks-the-cycle-started-by-zelda-skyward-sword/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Diablo 4: The Two Most Important Things to Do on Launch</title>
		<link>https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/diablo-4-the-two-most-important-things-to-do-on-launch/</link>
					<comments>https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/diablo-4-the-two-most-important-things-to-do-on-launch/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[Admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 04 Jun 2023 11:30:40 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[News]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/?p=7</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The launch of Diablo 4 is exciting for a number of reasons as the game takes the series to places it has never been before. As players are checking out all the new features in this entry and working on building their Diablo 4 characters with the best skills and equipment they can find, there ... <a title="Diablo 4: The Two Most Important Things to Do on Launch" class="read-more" href="https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/diablo-4-the-two-most-important-things-to-do-on-launch/" aria-label="More on Diablo 4: The Two Most Important Things to Do on Launch">Read more</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/diablo-4-the-two-most-important-things-to-do-on-launch/">Diablo 4: The Two Most Important Things to Do on Launch</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://test-preference-center.mattel.com">Preference Center  | Mattel</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p>The launch of Diablo 4 is exciting for a number of reasons as the game takes the series to places it has never been before. As players are checking out all the new features in this entry and working on building their Diablo 4 characters with the best skills and equipment they can find, there is sure to be a lot of content to uncover. However, while many fans are jumping into the game wanting to explore everything Sanctuary has to offer, there are two major things players need to do early in the game in order to boost their chances of survival against the onslaught of demons.</p>
<p>While these elements of the game might otherwise be overlooked, the betas for Diablo 4 demonstrated just how useful finding Altars of Lilith and obtaining Legendary Aspects can be for optimizing builds and the overall gameplay experience. The buffs and bonuses these mechanics provide can be invaluable to players in surviving into Diablo 4&#8217;s late game but are best obtained as soon as possible in order to maximize their benefits. As such, players should prioritize seeking out Altars of Lilith and clearing dungeons for their Legendary Aspects at launch.</p>
<p>A new mechanic introduced in this entry is Diablo 4&#8217;s Altars of Lilith, statues devoted to the Mother of Demons that can be found scattered throughout the game&#8217;s map. Finding and activating one of these altars gives the player a permanent increase to stats like Murmuring Obol Capacity, Dexterity, Intelligence, Willpower, or Strength. Starting off strong and building up a character&#8217;s stats through bonuses like this can help make leveling in the early hours of the game much more manageable and could make a huge difference when entering the endgame.</p>
<p>Another way to greatly increase the chances of survival in Diablo 4 is to optimize a character&#8217;s gear using Legendary Aspects. Typically, legendary items come with their own Aspects already affixed to the equipment, but Diablo 4 allows players to craft their own legendary gear by imprinting Legendary Aspects on rare-quality items to customize their build to meet their specific needs. In order to do so, players will need to acquire Legendary Aspects by either clearing a dungeon containing one and adding it to their Codex of Power or by extracting an Aspect from an existing legendary item they own.</p>
<p>Once a Diablo 4 player has their desired Legendary Aspect and has reached level 25, they can take them to the Occultist who can imprint the desired piece of gear with the Legendary Aspect. While players won&#8217;t be able to utilize this service right away, it&#8217;s in their best interest to fill up their Codex of Power with as many Aspects as they can by clearing specific dungeons in the early game so that they can get to work optimizing their equipment once they hit level 25. This service also comes with a high price tag, so it&#8217;s best to start saving gold early on and have a plan for mapping which Aspect should be imprinted onto which piece of gear to maximize cost efficiency.</p>
<p>Diablo 4 is available now in early access with its full launch coming June 6 for PC, PS4, PS5, Xbox One, and Xbox Series X/S.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/diablo-4-the-two-most-important-things-to-do-on-launch/">Diablo 4: The Two Most Important Things to Do on Launch</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="https://test-preference-center.mattel.com">Preference Center  | Mattel</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://test-preference-center.mattel.com/diablo-4-the-two-most-important-things-to-do-on-launch/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
